av8d.net 2016-10-18

# Privacy Policy : Kolbo Fine Judaica Gallery

We respect your privacy and treat it as though it was our own. Specifically we adhere strictly to the following policies: 

**_We absolutely do not share your personal information with any third parties and we do not provide our customer data base to anyone._**

### **Personal Information**

Any information you provide to us (such as your name, address, email, phone, and credit card information) is collected and used internally only for the purpose of fulfilling your orders or requests and better serving your needs. We are required to collect billing & shipping address information to ensure that your orders are processed accurately and in a timely manner. We do not collect information when you browse our website. Personal information is collected only if you voluntarily provide it. 

### **Customer Registration**

We encourage customers to register on our site so that you can have easy access to your history of purchases, wish lists, registries, and orders. It expedites returns or exchanges and allows fast and easy checkout for purchases. A customer account is not, however, necessary to make a purchase from our website. 

### **Email Addresses**

We may request your Email address at various places on our website for purposes of order tracking and confirmation, and important communication regarding our business with you. We also invite and encourage you to opt in to receive our newsletter so we can send you exciting information about new items, artists, special events and exhibits, promotions, and discounts. We are sensitive to the deluge of emails customers receive on a daily basis and, therefore, use the privilege of emailing you quite sparingly. We always provide an easy method to unsubscribe from future emails at the bottom of the page. And, under no circumstances do we share your email address with anyone. 

### **Links to Other Sites**

At times, given customer interest, we provide links to social media sites such as Facebook, Twitter, or Pinterest. Kolbo is not responsible for these websites, which have their own privacy policies and privacy practices. To the extent that your interaction with our website involves these other websites, you will be subject to their respective privacy policies, over which we have no control. If you visit our Kolbo website through a link from another website, you may be subject to that website’s privacy policy as well. If you choose to explore these websites and services, you may wish to carefully review their individual privacy policies. 

### **Data Security**

Kolbo Fine Judaica Gallery is a member in good standing of the Better Business Bureau. Financial transactions are protected through Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) and encryption technology. Access to any sensitive personal information is limited to staff that requires that information to complete a transaction on your behalf. 

### **Children**

Kolbo Fine Judaica Gallery, in compliance with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998, does not solicit or accept personal information from any child under the age of 13. Any transactions involving children under the age of 13 must be supervised and assisted by a parent or guardian. 

### **Privacy Policy Updates**

If we change or update this Privacy Policy, we will post changes and updates on our website. We encourage you to review this Privacy Policy from time to time so you will know if the Privacy Policy has been changed or updated. If you have any questions about the Privacy Policy, please do not hesitate to contact us.
